http://www.surmodics.com/privacy-policy/

Home | Privacy Policy
Privacy Policy
This Privacy Policy describes the current policies and practices of SurModics, Inc. ("SurModics") with regard to personal data collected by SurModics through this web site. The term “personal data” refers to personally identifiable information about you, such as your name, email address, telephone number, or mailing address, and any other information that is identified with you personally.
Personal Data Collected through SurModics.com
The only personal data SurModics currently collects through this web site is the information you give us when you use our site. For example, you may use this site to contact SurModics with your questions and comments or to request literature, white papers, or investor information. When you send us an email using one of the forms on this site, we ask you for your name and other contact information, including, your company’s name, your email address, your telephone number, and your mailing address or the mailing address of your company.
Use of Personal Data Collected through SurModics.com
SurModics uses the information you provide to respond to your email, answer your question, resolve your problem, and to maintain required correspondence files. No other attempts are made to identify individual users or their usage habits. We do not make any such information or your email address available to third parties.
Anonymous Data Collected through SurModics.com
In addition to the information you provide when you use our web site, SurModics may collect anonymous information about the use of our web site. For example, we may track how many visitors access our web site, the date and time of their visit, the length of their stay, and which pages they view. These statistics about our visitors and their use of our site may help SurModics to improve the content and functionality of our web site, to understand our customers better and markets, and to improve our products and services.
Links to Other Sites
SurModics does not control the privacy policies of the sites to which it provides links, and you should be aware that if you click through to such a site, you will be subject to that site’s privacy policies. SurModics uses industry-standard methods of securing its user information, such as, if and where appropriate, firewalls and limits on who can access user information. However, please keep in mind that there is no such thing as perfect security on the Internet.
Questions About Our Privacy Policy
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy or concerns about the way SurModics processes your personal data, please contact us.
